123mommy.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy Policy

This is the page that contains our privacy policy, for our portal 123 Mommy

**123Mommy Full Privacy**

123mommy.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. 123mommy.com does not collect any personal information.

**No IP address and no logging**

Your IP address is not used to gather broad demographic information and 123 Mommy does not track your general visiting paterns (how many pages you view while at one website, downloads, etc). We have no systems and no idea about how many users are on our website and what they are doing. The default logs on our server are disabled for speed, performance and privacy reasons. The log level is set on 'emerg' meaning the server will only create an emergency log in the event of a full server crash. Our mission is to create a safe online place with free online girl games, nothing more and nothing less.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit 123mommy.com. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**Sharing Of Information**

There are no scripts or programs running on our server that store your information. We allow our third party advertisers to host scripts on our webpages. Third party advertisers might collect, store and use your information. These scripts are not property of our game portal website and are subject to the privacy policy of the third party. Find the links to the third party privacy policies in the sections below to learn more.

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Please visit cpmstar.com and google.com/adsense to learn more about the current privacy policy of our third party services. The scripts and services of our third parties are not located on our server

Google Adsense : [www.google.com/adsense](https://www.google.com/adsense)  
Google Cookies Policy : [google.com/privacy_cookies.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_cookies.html)  
Adsense Privacy policy : [google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)  
Cpmstar Privacy Policy : [www.cpmstar.com](http://www.cpmstar.com/)

**Opt Out Cookies**

You can prevent the cookies being set by third party advertisers by visiting [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). This service is creating cookies itself too. Using this service is at your own risk, and girlgames24 shall not be responsible for using this service, in any way.

**What Are Cookies?**

Cookies are digital text files that can be created by any remote connection that you make in your browser. A cookie can only store text or (binairy) numbers or a combinations of both. Because cookies are just text files, created and controlled by your browser, it's a harmless system for your computer health. However you need to be aware that websites, mobile apps and advertisers are able to write and read certain 'invisible' information on the background while you think you are just browsing some online or mobile App content. Our website is NOT using performance cookies and is NOT tracking your behaviour. However we are using third-party advertisers that might use cookies - please read the third party section of our privacy policy for more information about our third parties.

**Liability**

It is 123mommy.com's policy to respond quickly to claims of intellectual property violation. Upon receiving notification in accordance with any related copyright organization or owner, 123mommy.com will immediately disable and remove games in question.
